<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Phoenix Journey - H@cking 'round the cable. Future is her3 '' Watch it @gain.</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/</link><description>Recent content on Phoenix Journey - H@cking 'round the cable. Future is her3 '' Watch it @gain.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:57:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nutek.neosb.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My First Website</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/posts/my-first-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/posts/my-first-website/</guid><description>Create YOUR first website Hej!
This New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve you have so many new resolutions that you need to get them into one place, and make them public, so you can be as transparent as your nearest politician is.
So you heard that there is GitHub, Nutek, Szymon, Hugo and whoever I have to mention to make you test this, because it&amp;rsquo;s so awesome to have your own static website build with Hugo Markdown and all crazy stuff.</description></item><item><title>Filling the Tank</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/posts/filling-the-tank/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 14:28:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/posts/filling-the-tank/</guid><description>Fuel ⛽️ for our rocket 🚀 Ground-up In previous post I tried to show you how to write simple program in neovim and run using python3. Today I want to fill in the gaps in your knowledge of my understanding of how developer work. First of all we will touch on some Vim commands that migh be useful and then we&amp;rsquo;ll build a tool that show where International Space Station is and who is currently in space.</description></item><item><title>Python &amp; Neovim</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/posts/python-neovim/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 19:37:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/posts/python-neovim/</guid><description>Programming language &amp;amp; text editor What do you need to have? Hej, today we begin learning with Nutek to be able to use it how I see it fit. First be sure you have one of the following:
neosb/nutek-core:0.4.0 from Docker Hub Nutek from crates.io or Github You could follow on with Python3, pip, venv and Neovim What you will learn? I want to show you few Python use cases and how to write code in Neovim.</description></item><item><title>Hi Nutek</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/posts/hi-nutek/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 11:01:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/posts/hi-nutek/</guid><description>Hello world Hi Nutek!
From deepest lows, to highest highs! I have my disguise, so to not fall into wrong eyes and pop out of surprise. I have my tools, I make my life. My house is on the rock. Rock &amp;rsquo;n Roll. From trashbin, to your soulmate.
Neosb &amp;amp; 😼</description></item></channel></rss>